<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Sip Craft Beer</title>
    <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Sip Craft Beer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Jolly Pumpkin - Kiviuq</title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/jolly-pumpkin-kiviuq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/jolly-pumpkin-kiviuq/</guid>
      <description>Beer’s intellectual. What a shame so many idiots drink it. ~Ray Bradbury
 As a born midwesterner I have a affinity to the beers of the region. My first taste of craft beer was a honey labeled beer out of Chippewa Falls, WI, and while it is no longer an independent brewery any more that doesn&amp;rsquo;t lessen the importance of the beer to my life. While I no longer live in the midwest and so I don&amp;rsquo;t get a normal fall anymore 1 but that means that I get to cling onto the summer beers that I enjoy even longer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mother Road - Tower Station</title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/mother-road-tower-station/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/mother-road-tower-station/</guid>
      <description>Northern Arizona&amp;hellip; surrounded by a fragrant piney forest under a peaceful turquoise sky&amp;hellip; what a perfect retreat, he thought, from the pace and pressure of modern living. ~Paul Harvey, &amp;ldquo;The Ghost and Don Dedera,&amp;rdquo; December 1972
 There is a reason the can is as blue as the sky above it, and the hops balance effortlessly between piney and citrusy. It all comes down to the magic that exists in one of a very few places where beer meets world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jester King - Figlet</title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/jester-king-figlet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/jester-king-figlet/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;There is a freedom you feel the closer you get to Austin, Texas.&amp;rdquo; - Willie Nelson
 If you have been to Texas Hill Country you hopefully learned about a couple of very important things, wide open spaces, the best BBQ in the world (yes, the world), and a little farmhouse just outside of Austin, TX.
I have been fortunate enough to have been to the brewery several times and it is highly recommended when the weather is nice in the spring or fall.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>