<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Sip Craft Beer</title>
    <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Sip Craft Beer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Bad Haiku Beer Review - Part Deux</title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/haiku-review-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/haiku-review-two/</guid>
      <description>Genuine poetry can communicate before it is understood. —T.S. Eliot
 Weathered Souls Brewing: Black is Beautiful
  Cause just as good as
    The dark sweet stout in the cans
    Everyone should brew this
  Prairie Artisan: Snickerdoodle Vanilla Noir
  Fourteen percent is
    Why I do not remember
    Cookie flavor bourbon stout</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bad Haiku Beer Review</title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/haiku-review-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/haiku-review-one/</guid>
      <description>Haiku is not a shriek, a howl, a sigh, or a yawn; rather, it is the deep breath of life. ― Santōka Taneda, Mountain Tasting: Haiku and Journals of Santoka Taneda
 Tombstone: All the Hops Double IPA
  All the hop are here
    Make it a double for fun
    Balanced is the key
  Historic: Pie Hole Porter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bucket List Beers - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/bucket-list-beers-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/bucket-list-beers-2/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I haven&amp;rsquo;t been everywhere but it&amp;rsquo;s on my list&amp;rdquo; - Paolo Coelho
 This is part 2 of my bucket list beers.
 Blackberry Farms - This kind of goes along with the Hills Farmstead (and the Trillium below), farmhouse brews are kind of my thing. While I enjoy all beers the idea of the beer having that terroir from the farm and the products that are possibly grown there is the beer experience is where my love of craft beer came from in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bucket List Beers - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/bucket-list-beers-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/bucket-list-beers-1/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The first thing on my bucket list is to fill the bucket with beer&amp;rdquo; - Unknown to the Author
 Everyone should have a bucket list, a list that has the adventure or experiences that a person feels compelled to accomplish before ones short time on this earth has completed. While I do have a list of places and experiences that I would like to do, I also keep a list of beers that I would like to taste/drink/consume in mass quantities before I decide that my life with beer has run its course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wrenhouse - Monte Vista</title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/wrenhouse-monte-vista/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/wrenhouse-monte-vista/</guid>
      <description>“Loneliness expresses the pain of being alone and solitude expresses the glory of being alone.” -Paul Tillich
 If you follow me on Instagram you noticed that I was reading The Great Alone: Walking the Pacific Crest Trail, it is a fantastic book by Tim Voors (Van Go) about his six month adventure hiking from Mexico all the way to Canada on the PCT. I highly recommend it, it is a quick easy ready as he effortlessly writes you through his experience, and it is his experience highlighting both the highs and the lows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Half Acre - Lager Town OktoberFest</title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/half-acre-oktoberfest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/half-acre-oktoberfest/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s a 106 miles to Chicago, we&amp;rsquo;ve got a full tank of gas, half a pack of cigarettes; it&amp;rsquo;s dark and we&amp;rsquo;re wearing sunglasses. Hit it!&amp;rdquo; - Elwood &amp;amp; Joliet Jake, The Blues Brothers
 I spent my college years in the Second City well before craft beer took over the city, at the time the only one that was there was Goose Island (the OG). The craft breweries that sprouted inside the city have made me really jealous of the current class of college students (and all the other people in general as well) who get to wander the city drinking a plethora of great craft beer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The heart of traveling</title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/travel-kid/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/travel-kid/</guid>
      <description>“Travel changes you. As you move through this life and this world you change things slightly, you leave marks behind, however small. And in return, life — and travel — leaves marks on you.” - Anthony Bourdain
 As long as I have been on this earth I have traveled across the country (and into a few other countries as well), it started with my family moving several times in my childhood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jolly Pumpkin - Kiviuq</title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/jolly-pumpkin-kiviuq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/jolly-pumpkin-kiviuq/</guid>
      <description>Beer’s intellectual. What a shame so many idiots drink it. ~Ray Bradbury
 As a born midwesterner I have a affinity to the beers of the region. My first taste of craft beer was a honey labeled beer out of Chippewa Falls, WI, and while it is no longer an independent brewery any more that doesn&amp;rsquo;t lessen the importance of the beer to my life. While I no longer live in the midwest and so I don&amp;rsquo;t get a normal fall anymore 1 but that means that I get to cling onto the summer beers that I enjoy even longer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mother Road - Tower Station</title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/mother-road-tower-station/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/mother-road-tower-station/</guid>
      <description>Northern Arizona&amp;hellip; surrounded by a fragrant piney forest under a peaceful turquoise sky&amp;hellip; what a perfect retreat, he thought, from the pace and pressure of modern living. ~Paul Harvey, &amp;ldquo;The Ghost and Don Dedera,&amp;rdquo; December 1972
 There is a reason the can is as blue as the sky above it, and the hops balance effortlessly between piney and citrusy. It all comes down to the magic that exists in one of a very few places where beer meets world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jester King - Figlet</title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/jester-king-figlet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/jester-king-figlet/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;There is a freedom you feel the closer you get to Austin, Texas.&amp;rdquo; - Willie Nelson
 If you have been to Texas Hill Country you hopefully learned about a couple of very important things, wide open spaces, the best BBQ in the world (yes, the world), and a little farmhouse just outside of Austin, TX.
I have been fortunate enough to have been to the brewery several times and it is highly recommended when the weather is nice in the spring or fall.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>