<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Saison on Sip Craft Beer</title>
    <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/tags/saison/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Saison on Sip Craft Beer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sipcraftbeer.com/tags/saison/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Wrenhouse - Monte Vista</title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/wrenhouse-monte-vista/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/wrenhouse-monte-vista/</guid>
      <description>“Loneliness expresses the pain of being alone and solitude expresses the glory of being alone.” -Paul Tillich
 If you follow me on Instagram you noticed that I was reading The Great Alone: Walking the Pacific Crest Trail, it is a fantastic book by Tim Voors (Van Go) about his six month adventure hiking from Mexico all the way to Canada on the PCT. I highly recommend it, it is a quick easy ready as he effortlessly writes you through his experience, and it is his experience highlighting both the highs and the lows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jolly Pumpkin - Kiviuq</title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/jolly-pumpkin-kiviuq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/jolly-pumpkin-kiviuq/</guid>
      <description>Beer’s intellectual. What a shame so many idiots drink it. ~Ray Bradbury
 As a born midwesterner I have a affinity to the beers of the region. My first taste of craft beer was a honey labeled beer out of Chippewa Falls, WI, and while it is no longer an independent brewery any more that doesn&amp;rsquo;t lessen the importance of the beer to my life. While I no longer live in the midwest and so I don&amp;rsquo;t get a normal fall anymore 1 but that means that I get to cling onto the summer beers that I enjoy even longer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>