<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sip Craft Beer</title>
    <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sip Craft Beer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sipcraftbeer.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Drinking Seasonally</title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/drinking-seasonally/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/drinking-seasonally/</guid>
      <description>Live each season as it passes; breathe the air, drink the drink, taste the fruit, and resign yourself to the influences of each. — Henry David Thoreau
 I love drinking beers based on the season, but what do you do when your &amp;lsquo;seasons&amp;rsquo; don&amp;rsquo;t match up with not only the rest of the world, but don&amp;rsquo;t align with the beer release calendar either.
I live somewhere in the mass metropolis of Phoenix, AZ and we don&amp;rsquo;t really get the normal four seasons that most of the rest of the county gets which make trying to drink seasonally a little challenging at times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>(un)Official Rules of Craft Beer - Gatherings</title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/rules-for-craft-beer-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/rules-for-craft-beer-1/</guid>
      <description>An intelligent man is sometimes forced to be drunk to spend time with his fools. – Ernest Hemingway
 Every year for the past twelve years, a group of my friend and I take a yearly pilgrimage up to Northern Arizona to come together and share all the beers we have been collecting over the previous year, along with massive amounts of poker playing. There are six of us so the beer selection is varied and vast, and we always seem to go home with some leftover beer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bad Haiku Beer Review - Part Deux</title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/haiku-review-two/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/haiku-review-two/</guid>
      <description>Genuine poetry can communicate before it is understood. —T.S. Eliot
 Weathered Souls Brewing: Black is Beautiful
  Cause just as good as
    The dark sweet stout in the cans
    Everyone should brew this
  Prairie Artisan: Snickerdoodle Vanilla Noir
  Fourteen percent is
    Why I do not remember
    Cookie flavor bourbon stout</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bad Haiku Beer Review</title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/haiku-review-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/haiku-review-one/</guid>
      <description>Haiku is not a shriek, a howl, a sigh, or a yawn; rather, it is the deep breath of life. ― Santōka Taneda, Mountain Tasting: Haiku and Journals of Santoka Taneda
 Tombstone: All the Hops Double IPA
  All the hop are here
    Make it a double for fun
    Balanced is the key
  Historic: Pie Hole Porter</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bucket List Beers - Part 2</title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/bucket-list-beers-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/bucket-list-beers-2/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;I haven&amp;rsquo;t been everywhere but it&amp;rsquo;s on my list&amp;rdquo; - Paolo Coelho
 This is part 2 of my bucket list beers.
 Blackberry Farms - This kind of goes along with the Hills Farmstead (and the Trillium below), farmhouse brews are kind of my thing. While I enjoy all beers the idea of the beer having that terroir from the farm and the products that are possibly grown there is the beer experience is where my love of craft beer came from in the first place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bucket List Beers - Part 1</title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/bucket-list-beers-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/bucket-list-beers-1/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The first thing on my bucket list is to fill the bucket with beer&amp;rdquo; - Unknown to the Author
 Everyone should have a bucket list, a list that has the adventure or experiences that a person feels compelled to accomplish before ones short time on this earth has completed. While I do have a list of places and experiences that I would like to do, I also keep a list of beers that I would like to taste/drink/consume in mass quantities before I decide that my life with beer has run its course.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wrenhouse - Monte Vista</title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/wrenhouse-monte-vista/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/wrenhouse-monte-vista/</guid>
      <description>“Loneliness expresses the pain of being alone and solitude expresses the glory of being alone.” -Paul Tillich
 If you follow me on Instagram you noticed that I was reading The Great Alone: Walking the Pacific Crest Trail, it is a fantastic book by Tim Voors (Van Go) about his six month adventure hiking from Mexico all the way to Canada on the PCT. I highly recommend it, it is a quick easy ready as he effortlessly writes you through his experience, and it is his experience highlighting both the highs and the lows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Half Acre - Lager Town OktoberFest</title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/half-acre-oktoberfest/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/half-acre-oktoberfest/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;It&amp;rsquo;s a 106 miles to Chicago, we&amp;rsquo;ve got a full tank of gas, half a pack of cigarettes; it&amp;rsquo;s dark and we&amp;rsquo;re wearing sunglasses. Hit it!&amp;rdquo; - Elwood &amp;amp; Joliet Jake, The Blues Brothers
 I spent my college years in the Second City well before craft beer took over the city, at the time the only one that was there was Goose Island (the OG). The craft breweries that sprouted inside the city have made me really jealous of the current class of college students (and all the other people in general as well) who get to wander the city drinking a plethora of great craft beer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The heart of traveling</title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/travel-kid/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/travel-kid/</guid>
      <description>“Travel changes you. As you move through this life and this world you change things slightly, you leave marks behind, however small. And in return, life — and travel — leaves marks on you.” - Anthony Bourdain
 As long as I have been on this earth I have traveled across the country (and into a few other countries as well), it started with my family moving several times in my childhood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jolly Pumpkin - Kiviuq</title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/jolly-pumpkin-kiviuq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/jolly-pumpkin-kiviuq/</guid>
      <description>Beer’s intellectual. What a shame so many idiots drink it. ~Ray Bradbury
 As a born midwesterner I have a affinity to the beers of the region. My first taste of craft beer was a honey labeled beer out of Chippewa Falls, WI, and while it is no longer an independent brewery any more that doesn&amp;rsquo;t lessen the importance of the beer to my life. While I no longer live in the midwest and so I don&amp;rsquo;t get a normal fall anymore 1 but that means that I get to cling onto the summer beers that I enjoy even longer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mother Road - Tower Station</title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/mother-road-tower-station/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/mother-road-tower-station/</guid>
      <description>Northern Arizona&amp;hellip; surrounded by a fragrant piney forest under a peaceful turquoise sky&amp;hellip; what a perfect retreat, he thought, from the pace and pressure of modern living. ~Paul Harvey, &amp;ldquo;The Ghost and Don Dedera,&amp;rdquo; December 1972
 There is a reason the can is as blue as the sky above it, and the hops balance effortlessly between piney and citrusy. It all comes down to the magic that exists in one of a very few places where beer meets world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 19:57:09 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Sip Craft Beer! If you got this far congrats you have entered my little part of internet where I plan on writing mostly about craft beer, which is where most of my adventures end up leading me towards.
It may get a little weird around here as well, so just remember you have been warned.
They say that a good craft beer will allow you to remember the time and place that you enjoyed it, and that a great beer will also taste better if you share it with others.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Me</title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 19:57:09 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>If you feel like getting a hold of someone.
You can follow me on Instagram @sipcraftbeer
Or you can email me at sipcraftbeer@gmail.com
Prost!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jester King - Figlet</title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/jester-king-figlet/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/jester-king-figlet/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;There is a freedom you feel the closer you get to Austin, Texas.&amp;rdquo; - Willie Nelson
 If you have been to Texas Hill Country you hopefully learned about several very important things, wide open spaces, the best BBQ in the world (yes, the world), and a little farmhouse just outside of Austin, TX.
I have been fortunate enough to have been to the brewery several times and it is highly recommended when the weather is nice in the spring or fall.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/craft/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/craft/</guid>
      <description>how to appreciate the craft that goes into making things. understanding the scale reviving old techiniques appricating the ingrediants learning how they affect the beer why the same beer might be different</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/intro_rules/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sipcraftbeer.com/post/intro_rules/</guid>
      <description>What this blog will be about
 There is occasion for every beer, and a beer for every occasion   Macro beers are okay as well as craft Don&amp;rsquo;t pick the wrong beer   Great..Good&amp;hellip;Everything else   jonathan gold method of talking about beers that are good. Never talk bad about beer (even bad beers take a lot of work by people to make)  Taste is just the entry point, how does the beer make you feel (reference Grant)   Taste is for pussy&amp;rsquo;s so many other places that people tell you how the beer tastes i want to know how the beer makes you feel when you drink it   Terroir is just as relevant for beer as it is for other beverages   where the ingredients in your beer should matter as much as the grapes matter in wine how does the final product change with the way, methods, and conditions that the ingredients were grown the same beer being different in different years shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be considered a bad thing  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>